User Study 12/4/2012

Issues: 

People name places that don't exist in the Places API. 
We should, if the place doesn't exist, ask them to give us an address for that place.
This, or we make two text fields: One for the place name (optional), and one for its address. 
Then, we make place names an array in our places db. 

Event back button not firing correctly. It now just redirects to /events/feed

There's not a whole lot of instruction as far as what to do on the event page. (I'm adding tooltips)


